Register of the William T. Poole collection
Hoover Institution Archives
- Un-American Activities Subject File, 1920-1976 (Box 51-231.)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference. Circular letters, press releases, leaflets, flyers, newsletter, clippings, radio broadcast summary, and court testimony re Ralph Abernathy, 1965-1973. (Folder 185: 14)
    See also King, Martin Luther, Jr.
  - Southern Conference Educational Fund. (Folder 185)
    See also Southern Conference for Human Welfare
    - Correspondence, 1954-1974. (Folder 185: 15)
    - Southern Conference Educational Fund issuances (Folder 186)
      - General. Leaflets, flyers, circulars, journal article reprints, and press releases, 1948-1973 (Folder 186: 1)
      - Southern Patriot. Serial issues (Folder 186)
        - 1947-1959 (Folder 186: 2)
        - 1960-1965 (Folder 186: 3)
        - 1966-1974 (Folder 186: 4)
      - Pamphlets (Birmingham: People in Motion; House Un-American Activities Committee: Bulwark of Segregation; "My Beliefs and My Associations Are None of the Business of This Committee"; The Right to Organize; The Untouchables), ca. 1960-1972 (Folder 186: 5)
      - Internal documents. Reports, statements, proposals, and memoranda, 1958-1974. (Folder 187: 1)
        Includes material relating to resignations of Anne Braden and Carl Braden
    - Material about the Southern Conference Educational Fund. Statement, clippings, other printed matter, and HUAC memoranda, 1958-1974 (Folder 187: 2)
  - Southern Conference for Human Welfare. (Folder 187)
    - General. Letters, leaflets, flyers, programs, conference proceedings, press release, serial issues (Southern Patriot), and pamphlets (For Your Children, Too; The Poll Tax), 1938-1947 (Folder 187: 3)
    - Mailing lists, undated (Folder 187: 4)
    - Material about the Southern Conference for Human Welfare. Clippings, journal article, and photocopy of book (And Promises to Keep: The Southern Conference for Human Welfare, 1938-1948), 1938-1967 (Folder 187: 5)
  - Southern Coordinating Committee to End the War in Vietnam. Letter, flyers, newsletters, and clippings, 1966 (Folder 187: 6)
  - Southern Poverty Law Center [Montgomery, Alabama]. Circular letter and leaflet, 1972 (Folder 187: 7)
  - Southern Regional Council [Atlanta]. Report ("Events at Orangeburg" [South Carolina]), 1968 (Folder 187: 8)
  - Southern Student Organizing Committee [Nashville] (Folder 187)
    - General. Letter, prospectus, flyers, newsletters, clippings, and HUAC memorandum, 1964-1969 (Folder 187: 9)
    - New South Student. Serial issues, 1965-1966 (Folder 187: 10)
  - Soviet Russia Today (Folder 188)
    - General. Circular letter and printed articles from the journal, 1937-1947 (Folder 188: 1)
    - Serial issues (Folder 188)
      - 1934-1940 (Folder 188: 2)
      - 1941-1942 (Folder 188: 3)
      - 1943-1946 (Folder 188: 4)
      - 1947-1949 (Folder 188: 5)
  - Soviet Union (Folder 188)
    - Soviet government English-language issuances (Folder 188)
      - Serial issues and printed articles from journals (Folder 188)
        - General (Information Bulletin; International Affairs; Moscow News; Smena; Soviet News; Sputnik), 1965-1971 (Folder 188: 6)
        - New Times, 1950-1974., Includes accompanying HISC memorandum (Folder 189: 1)
        - Pamphlets (Americans Look at Soviet Life; Anti-Communism: The Main Line of Zionism; The Korean Question; Lenin on the Emancipation of Women; Soviet Jews; The Teachings of Lenin and Stalin on Proletarian Revolution and the State; Zionism: Instrument of Imperialist Reaction) and printed miscellany, 1937-1972 (Folder 189: 2)
    - Material about the Soviet Union (Folder 189)
      - General. Clippings, printed articles and printed excerpts, United Nations circulars re deportations in Estonia, U.S. Department of State release of Nikita Khrushchev 20th Communist Party Congress speech, pamphlet (The Kronstadt Rebellion), and HUAC memorandum, 1922-1973 (Folder 189: 3)
      - U.S. Department of State publication (Soviet World Outlook: A Handbook of Communist Statements), 1959 (Folder 189: 4)
      - U.S. Foreign Broadcast Information Service radio broadcast summaries (Folder 189)
        - 1956 (20th Communist Party Congress) (Folder 189: 5)
        - 1956 (20th Communist Party Congress) (contd.) (Folder 190: 1)
        - 1959 (21st Communist Party Congress) (Folder 190: 2-5)
        - 1964-1973 (Folder 191: 1)
  - Spain. Issuances of miscellaneous organizations re solidarity with people of Spain, including circular letters, flyers, and printed articles, 1938-1970. (Folder 191: 2)
    Includes Medical Bureau and North American Committee to Aid Spanish Democracy, Spanish Refugee Aid, Spanish Refugee Relief Campaign, Trade Union Committee for Spanish Refugees, United American Spanish Aid Committee, and others
  - Spanish Refugee Appeal of the Joint Anti-Fascist Refugee Committee. Circular letters, 1951-1954 (Folder 191: 3)
  - Spartacist League (Folder 191)
    - Correspondence, 1965-1971 (Folder 191: 4)
    - Spartacist League issuances (Folder 191)
      - General. Flyers and newsletters (Revolutionary Marxist Caucus Newsletter), 1965-1971 (Folder 191: 5)
      - Spartacist. Serial issues, 1965-1971 (Folder 191: 6)
      - Workers' Action/Workers Vanguard. Serial issues, 1971-1974. (Folder 191: 7)
        Includes accompanying HISC memoranda
    - Material about the Spartacist League. HUAC memoranda, with accompanying Spartacist League issuance exhibits, ca. 1966-1967 (Folder 191: 8)
  - Spider. Printed article from the journal re Vietnam War, and HUAC memoranda, 1965 (Folder 191: 9)
  - Spock, Benjamin. Letter, flyers, printed appeals, petition, U.S. Department of Justice press releases, and clippings, 1965-1968 (Folder 191: 10)
  - Spock Defense Fund [re Benjamin Spock]. Circulars, 1968 (Folder 191: 11)
  - Spring Mobilization Committee to End the War in Vietnam. (Folder 191)
    - Correspondence, 1967 (Folder 191: 12)
    - Spring Mobilization Committee to End the War in Vietnam issuances. Minutes, report, letterhead data, leaflets, flyers, printed appeals, and circulars, 1966-1967 (Folder 191: 13)
    - Material about the Spring Mobilization Committee to End the War in Vietnam. Clippings, printed articles, HUAC memoranda, and HUAC printed report (Communist Origin and Manipulation of Vietnam Week), 1967 (Folder 192: 1)
  - Spring Movement [re Vietnam War]. Circulars, 1971 (Folder 192: 2)
  - Stamler, Jeremiah. Letter, petition, list of endorsers, and Congressional speech, 1966 (Folder 192: 3)
    See also Jeremiah Stamler, M.D. Legal Aid Fund
  - Stanford Committee for Peace in Vietnam [Stanford University]. Printed appeal, flyer, and clippings, 1965-1966 (Folder 192: 5)
  - Stanford Vietnam Day Committee [Stanford University]. Printed appeal, 1965 (Folder 192: 5)
  - State, County and Municipal Workers of America. Circular letters, resolutions, and flyers, 1937-1941 (Folder 192: 6)
  - Stockholm Conference on Vietnam. Circular letters, newsletters, speeches, statements, reports, and resolutions (Folder 192)
    - 1967-1969 (Folder 192: 7)
    - 1970 (Folder 192: 8)
    - 1971-1974 (Folder 192: 9)
  - Stop the Draft Week Committee. Flyers, circulars, and clippings, 1967-1968 (Folder 192: 10)
  - Strong, Anna Louise. Letter and newsletter (Today) by Strong, 1951-1956 (Folder 192: 11)
  - Student Committee to Send Medical Aid to the Front of Liberation of South Vietnam. Letters, Philadelphia police report, and clippings, 1964-1966 (Folder 192: 12)
  - Student Health Organization [Chicago]. Clippings, 1969 (Folder 192: 13)
  - Student Mobilization Committee to End the War in Vietnam (Folder 193)
    - Correspondence, 1967-1973. (Folder 193: 1)
    - Student Mobilization Committee to End the War in Vietnam issuances (Folder 193)
      - General. Leaflets, flyers, circulars, press releases, speeches, and statements, 1967-1973 (Folder 193: 2-3)
      - GI Press Service. Serial issues, 1969-1971 (Folder 193: 4)
      - Student Mobilizer. Serial issues (Folder 194)
        - 1967-1968 (Folder 194: 1)
        - 1969 (Folder 194: 2)
        - 1970-1972 (Folder 194: 3)
      - Internal documents. Report, agenda, memoranda, proposals, resolutions, circulars, and newsletters, 1968-1971 (Folder 194: 4)
      - Emergency National Conference (Cleveland, 1970 June). Agenda and proposals of the conference, but mainly literature distributed at the conference by other organizations, notably the Socialist Workers Party (Folder 195: 1)
    - Material about the Student Mobilization Committee to End the War in Vietnam. Clippings, printed articles, informant's reports, HUAC memoranda and press releases, and HUAC printed report (Communist Origin and Manipulation of Vietnam Week), 1967-1971 (Folder 195: 2)
  - Student Nonviolent Coordinating Committee [SNCC] (Folder 195)
    - Student Nonviolent Coordinating Committee issuances. Circular letters, report, statements, press releases, flyers, leaflets, and newsletters (Student Voice), 1964-1968 (Folder 195: 3)
    - Material about the Student Nonviolent Coordinating Committee. Clippings, printed articles, White Party flyer, and HUAC memorandum and organizational chart, 1965-1973 (Folder 195: 4)
  - Student Partisan Alliance [University of Hawaii]. Clipping, 1965 (Folder 195: 5)
  - Student Peace Union. Letter, programmatic statement, flyers, newsletters, bulletins, pamphlet (The Pacifist Ethic and Humanism), clippings, printed articles, and HUAC memoranda, 1960-1967 (Folder 195: 6)
  - Student Union for Peace Action [Canada]. Clippings and printed article, 1966-1967 (Folder 195: 7)
  - Students (General) (Folder 195)
    - Issuances of miscellaneous student groups (Folder 195)
      - General. Letters, leaflets, flyers, circulars, newsletters, mailing lists, and pamphlets (Community Market Catalog; Why We Strike [Columbia University]), 1941-1973 (Folder 195: 8)
      - Student newspapers and printed articles from student newspapers (Folder 195)
        - Daily Californian [University of California, Berkeley], 1969-1971 (Folder 196: 1)
        - Hatchet [George Washington University], 1967-1972 (Folder 196: 2)
        - Torch [Roosevelt University], 1971 (Folder 196: 3)
          Includes HISC memorandum
        - Tower [Catholic University], 1971 (Folder 196: 4)
        - Miscellaneous colleges, 1961-1973 (Folder 196: 5)
        - High schools, 1969-1971 (Folder 196: 6)
    - Material about student movements (Folder 196)
      - General. Reports, bulletins, pamphlets (The Conspiracy against the Schools; The "Left Swing" in Education; Nothing but Praise: Thoughts on the Ties between Higher Education and the Federal Government), Congressional speeches, and miscellany, 1941-1973 (Folder 196: 7)
      - Clippings and printed articles, 1943-1972 (Folder 196: 8)
      - Campus Coalition issuances [organization opposing student radicalism]. Statement of principles, press releases, and circulars, 1970-1971 (Folder 197: 1)
  - Students against the Rank [University of Chicago]. Clippings, 1966 (Folder 197: 2)
  - Students for a Democratic Society (Folder 197)
    - Correspondence, 1965-1970. (Folder 197: 3)
    - Students for a Democratic Society issuances (Folder 197)
      - General. Press releases, printed appeals, leaflets, flyers, and circulars, 1965-1972 (Folder 197: 4)
      - Newsletters, 1965-1969 (Folder 197: 5)
      - New Left Notes (Folder 197)
        - 1966-1968 (Folder 197: 6)
        - 1969 (Folder 197: 7)
        - 1970 (Folder 198: 1)
        - 1971-1973 and undated (Folder 198: 2)
      - Miscellaneous serial issues (Activist; Caw!; Fight to Win; Radical America; Red Balloon), 1962-1971 (Folder 198: 3)
      - Pamphlets (Ally with Campus Workers; E.R.A.P. and How It Grew; Guide to Conscientious Objection; Manchild in the Corporate State: Cornell's Ruling Elite and the National Economy; SDS Work-In 1968; Vietnam: No Mistake!; Who Controls Vietnam?), 1967-1970 (Folder 198: 4)
      - "The Port Huron Statement," 1962 (Folder 198: 5)
      - Internal documents. Memoranda, proposals, resolutions, position papers, and schedules, 1966-1969 (Folder 198: 6)
    - Material about Students for a Democratic Society (Folder 198)
      - General. Printed articles, press releases, Church League of America pamphlet (Students for a Democratic Society [SDS], and Herald of Freedom intelligence report), 1965-1970 (Folder 198: 7)
      - Government documents. HUAC/HISC and Federal Bureau of Investigation memoranda and organizational chart, informants' reports, Congressional speech, and HUAC/HISC hearing testimony and exhibit, 1965-1969 (Folder 199: 1)
      - Clippings (Folder 199)
        - 1964-1965 (Folder 199: 2)
        - 1966 (Folder 199: 3)
        - 1967 (Folder 199: 4)
        - 1968 (Folder 199: 5)
        - 1969-1970 (Folder 199: 6)
  - Students for Democratic Action. Clippings, 1965-1966 (Folder 200: 1)
  - Students for Peace in Vietnam [Students for a Democratic Society high school affiliate]. Speech, printed article, and clippings, 1965-1966 (Folder 200: 2)
  - Sullivan, Terry. Clippings, 1966 (Folder 200: 3)
  - Sullivan County Committee for Peace in Vietnam [Sullivan County, New York]. Letters and clipping, 1965-1966 (Folder 200: 4)
  - Summer Liberation School [Columbia University]. Catalog, ca. 1969 (Folder 200: 5)
  - Summer of Support [re GI dissidents; Chicago]. Circular letters, printed appeals, and clippings, 1968 (Folder 200: 6)
  - Supporting Committee [re draft resisters; New York City]. Flyer, 1967 (Folder 200: 7)
  - Takoma Park-Silver Spring Community Forum on Vietnam [Silver Spring, Maryland]. Flyer, 1968 (Folder 200: 8)
  - Taxpayers against War [San Francisco]. Circular, 1967 (Folder 200: 9)
  - Taxpayers Campaign for Urban Priorities [New York City]. Printed appeal, 1969 (Folder 200: 10)
  - Taylor, William Earl. Clipping, 1965 (Folder 200: 11)
  - Teachers Committee for Peace in Vietnam. Letter, circulars, flyers, newsletters, printed appeals, and clippings, 1965-1969 (Folder 200: 12)
  - Teachers Concerned about Vietnam [Baltimore]. Printed appeal and clipping, 1967 (Folder 200: 13)
  - Teachers Defense Committee [California]. Circular letter, flyers, and printed appeal, 1959 (Folder 200: 14)
  - Teachers Union. Newsletter and clipping, 1948-1950 (Folder 200: 15)
  - Teach-ins [re Vietnam War]. Printed articles, clippings, and U.S. Senate Judiciary Committee staff study (The Anti-Vietnam Agitation and the Teach-In Movement), 1965 (Folder 200: 16)
  - Ted Weiss for Congress. New York Congressional election flyer, 1966 (Folder 200: 17)
  - Temporary Organizing Committee for a Marxist-Leninist Youth Organization. Circular letter, statement, position papers, printed articles, and HISC memoranda, 1969-1970 (Folder 200: 18)
    See also Young Workers Liberation League.
  - Tenth Street Residents Opposed to the War in Vietnam [New York City]. Printed appeals and clipping, 1967-1968 (Folder 200: 19)
  - Texas Observer. Serial issues, 1971 (Folder 200: 20)
  - Theatre Arts Committee. Circular letters, printed articles, and serial issues (TAC; TAC Magazine), 1938-1940 (Folder 200: 21)
  - Third Press [black publishing company; New York City]. Circular letter, advertisements, printed articles, and clippings, 1970-1971 (Folder 200: 22)
  - Third World Liberation Front. Circular letter, flyers, and clippings, 1969 (Folder 200: 23)
  - Third World Women's Alliance. Serial issue, 1973 (Folder 200: 24)
  - Thomas, Norman. Clippings, 1966 (Folder 200: 25)
    See also Norman Thomas Endowment, and Norman Thomas Fund
  - Thomas Jefferson Art Gallery [Santa Monica, California]. Leaflets, 1946 (Folder 200: 26)
  - Times Square Demonstration Committee [re Vietnam War; New York City]. Clipping, 1966 (Folder 200: 27)
  - Trade Union Action Conference for Peace. Statements and leaflet, 1952 (Folder 200: 28)
  - Trade Union Sponsoring Committee for a Labor Party Conference. Press release, agenda, resolutions, and minutes, 1936 (Folder 200: 29)
  - Trade Union Unity League. Serial issue (Labor Unity), and pamphlets (The Trade Union Unity League; The Trade Unions since the N.R.A.), 1934 (Folder 200: 30)
  - Trade Unionists for a Labor Party [New York City]. Flyers, 1967 (Folder 200: 31)
  - Trade Unionists for Peace. Circular letters, statements, flyers, leaflets, and HUAC memorandum, 1965-1966 (Folder 200: 32)
  - Treuhaft, Robert E. Photocopies of financial records of Treuhaft's election campaign for district attorney of Alameda County, California, 1966 (Folder 200: 33)
  - Tri-Continental Information Center [New York City]. Letter, bulletins, circulars, and clipping, 1967-1968 (Folder 201: 1)
  - Turn toward Peace. Leaflets, flyers, and circulars, 1962-1965 (Folder 201: 2)
  - Tyndall, Timothy. Clipping, 1965 (Folder 201: 3)
  - U.S.-China People's Friendship Association. Newsletters and flyers, 1972-1973 (Folder 201: 4)
  - U.S. Committee for a Democratic Spain. Letters, bulletins, and flyers, 1971-1975 (Folder 201: 5)
  - U.S. Committee for Cooperation with the Japan Council against A and H Bombs. Flyer and pamphlet (Report from Hiroshima), 1962 (Folder 201: 6)
  - U.S. Committee for Democracy in Greece. Circular letters and serial issue (Report on Greece), 1968 (Folder 201: 7)
  - U.S. Committee to Aid the National Liberation Front of South Vietnam. Letters, statements, circulars, leaflets, flyers, printed articles, clippings, HUAC memoranda, and photocopies of index card file, 1965-1970 (Folder 201: 8)
  - U.S. Farmers' Association. Circular letter, serial issues (U.S. Farm News), and pamphlet (The Truth about the Farm Betrayals), 1968-1971 (Folder 201: 9)
  - U.S. Week. Serial issues, 1941 (Folder 201: 10)
  - Underground Press Syndicate. Leaflet and list of member publications, ca. 1973 (Folder 201: 11)
  - Union Democracy in Action. Serial issue, 1964 (Folder 201: 12)
  - Union for Democratic Action. Circulars, letterhead data, list of conference delegates, leaflet, printed articles, and clipping, 1941-1947 (Folder 201: 13)
  - Union of Concerned Scientists. Circular letter, and pamphlets (ABM ABC; MIRV), 1969 (Folder 201: 14)
  - Unitarians (General). Letter, press release, speech, statement, resolutions, circulars, printed appeals, and clipping, 1951-1973 (Folder 201: 15)
  - United Blacks against Genocide [Brooklyn]. Flyer, ca. 1967 (Folder 201: 16)
  - United Committee against the War [Berkeley]. Circular letter, letterhead data, and clipping, 1966 (Folder 201: 17)
  - United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America (Folder 201)
    - Correspondence, 1953-1970. (Folder 201: 18)
    - United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America issuances (Folder 201)
      - General. Flyers, leaflets, circulars, and printed appeals, 1943-1956 (Folder 201: 19)
      - UE News. Serial issues and printed articles from the journal, 1943-1967 (Folder 201: 20)
    - Material about the United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America. Leaflets, flyers, circulars, printed articles, pamphlet (10 Years of Communist Control of UE), and HUAC memoranda, 1949-1956. (Folder 202: 1)
      Includes issuances of the International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, and of the International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers
  - United Farm Workers. Letter, statement, leaflets, and flyers, 1969-1974 (Folder 202: 2)
  - United Federal Workers of America. Letters, statement, resolutions, and flyers, 1937-1939 (Folder 202: 3)
  - United for Peace [Westbury, New York]. Serial issue (United for Peace Reporter) and clipping, 1967 (Folder 202: 4)
  - United Front for Political Defense [Cleveland]. Flyer, 1969 (Folder 202: 5)
  - United Furniture Workers of America. Letter, resolution, and report, 1938-1950 (Folder 202: 6)
  - United May Day Committee. Circular letters, leaflets, flyers, printed articles, and clippings, 1938-1957 (Folder 202: 7)
  - United Methodist Church (Folder 202)
    - General. Circular letters, reports, leaflets, reprints, and circulars, 1956-1971 (Folder 202: 8)
    - Serial issues (Concern; Engage; Motive), 1967-1971 (Folder 202: 9)
  - United Nations Association of the United States of America. Press release, circulars, and printed articles, 1942-1973 (Folder 202: 10)
  - United Office and Professional Workers of America. Circular letters, press releases, resolutions, report, leaflets, flyers, and clippings, 1937-1951 (Folder 202: 11)
  - United Protest Memorial Meeting (Los Angeles, 1966) [re shootings of Young Socialist Alliance members in Detroit]. Flyers (Folder 202: 12)
  - United Retail and Wholesale Employees of America. Circular letters and flyers, 1938-1940 (Folder 202: 13)
  - United Serviceman's Actions for Freedom [re GI dissidents; Dayton, Ohio]. Newsletter, 1969 (Folder 202: 14)
  - United States Committee for Justice to Latin American Political Prisoners. Letters, statement, circulars, and serial issues (USLA Reporter), 1967-1970 (Folder 203: 1)
  - United States Labor Party. Congressional testimony, 1975 (Folder 203: 2)
  - United States. National Recovery Administration. Clippings, 1933 (Folder 203: 3)
  - United States National Student Association. (Folder 203)
    See also People's Peace Treaty
    - Correspondence, 1969-1970 (Folder 203: 4)
    - United States National Student Association issuances (Folder 203)
      - General. Constitution and bylaws, congress program, financial reports, press releases, circulars, flyers, and pamphlet (What Is NSA?), 1965-1973 (Folder 203: 5)
      - Newsletters, 1970-1971 (Folder 203: 6)
    - Material about the United States National Student Association. Clippings, flyers, U.S. Department of State statement, and Students to Oppose Participation in the National Student Association report, 1966-1971 (Folder 203: 7)
  - United States Servicemen's Fund [re GI dissidents]. Letter and newsletters (About Face!), 1972-1973 (Folder 203: 8)
  - United World Federalists. Printed appeals, clippings, and pamphlet (How to Give the United Nations the Power to Enforce World Peace through World Law), 1966-1967 (Folder 203: 9)
  - Universities Committee against ABM [Anti-Ballistic Missile]. Printed appeals, 1969 (Folder 203: 10)
  - Universities Committee on Problems of War and Peace. Printed appeal, 1965 (Folder 203: 11)
  - Universities National Anti-War Fund. Circular letters, 1970 (Folder 203: 12)
  - University Christian Movement. Articles of operation, report, leaflets, and circulars, 1966-1968 (Folder 203: 13)
  - University Circle Teach-In Committee [Cleveland]. Circular letters, 1967 (Folder 203: 14)
  - University Committee to Protest the War in Vietnam [New York State]. Printed appeal, 1965 (Folder 203: 15)
  - University of California antiwar protests. Flyers, printed appeal, and clippings, 1965-1968 (Folder 204: 1)
  - University of Chicago antiwar protests. Clippings, 1966-1967 (Folder 204: 2)
  - University of Connecticut antiwar protests. Clippings, 1968 (Folder 204: 3)
  - University of Dayton antiwar protests. Clipping, 1967 (Folder 204: 4)
  - University of Florida antiwar protests. Flyers and clippings, 1966 (Folder 204: 5)
  - University of Hawaii antiwar protests. Clippings, 1967-1968 (Folder 204: 6)
  - University of Iowa antiwar protests. Clippings, 1967-1968 (Folder 204: 7)
  - University of Maryland antiwar protests. Clippings, 1965-1967 (Folder 204: 8)
  - University of Michigan antiwar protests. Flyers, student publications, clippings, and HUAC memorandum, 1965-1967 (Folder 204: 9)
  - University of Minnesota antiwar protests. Clippings, 1966-1967 (Folder 204: 10)
  - University of Notre Dame antiwar protests. Clipping, 1967 (Folder 204: 11)
  - University of Oklahoma antiwar protests. Clippings, 1966 (Folder 204: 12)
  - University of Pennsylvania antiwar protests. Clippings, 1966-1968 (Folder 204: 13)
  - University of Texas antiwar protests. Clippings, 1967-1968 (Folder 204: 14)